<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_ball.zip</path>
		<name>Ball</name>
		<desc>"Ball" was the very first "Game &amp; Watch" handheld game ever made by Nintendo on April 28,1980. It was part of the "Silver" series, which later spawned the popular "Gold" series.</desc>
		<releasedate>19800428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_bfightn.zip</path>
		<name>Bomb Fight</name>
		<desc>An angry lion is throwing bombs to a peaceful elephant. Playing the elephant, you have to spit water to bombs to defuse them before they explode. Misses: one miss per exploded bomb. Three misses and game ends. 10 points are awarded when the elephant successfully defuses a bomb. All bombs are cleared at every 1000 points. Maximum displayed score is 9999.</desc>
		<releasedate>19820101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>VTech</developer>
		<publisher>VTech</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_bjack.zip</path>
		<name>Black Jack</name>
		<desc>The game is simply Black Jack on an LCD screen. The game is very different from the standard Game &amp; Watch games. If your cards amount to a combined number of 21, then you win the game. Black Jack is the last Game &amp; Watch video games to be released in Japan. All games released after Black Jack were released only in other countries, despite being made in Japan.</desc>
		<releasedate>19850215T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Casino / Cards</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_boxing.zip</path>
		<name>Boxing</name>
		<desc>You're the character on the right and the opponent is on the left. At the top is the status of both characters. The maximum amount of health a character can have is five bars, though the opponent will often have less at the beginning of the game. Once you knock your opponent out, he'll move farther to the left and will get back up again. If you lost any health before you knocked him out the first time, your health will be regained. If he knocks you out, you'll move to the right and get back up.</desc>
		<releasedate>19840731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Boxing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_bsweep.zip</path>
		<name>Bomb Sweeper</name>
		<desc>Dynamite Jack, a masked bomber, has planted many bombs in the sewers. You play the role of John Solver, who must descend into the sewer and defuse the bombs before it's too late!

Using the D-pad to move John Solver, you must reach at least one of the bombs hidden in the walls to clear the screen and receive a bonus for the time remaining. The only obstacles in your path are the walls, which you must either maneuver around or push them along provided there is no obstruction in the way. Some levels are a test of speed, others are a test of logic and intelligence.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_cgrab.zip</path>
		<name>Crab Grab</name>
		<desc>Crab Grab is a Super Color Game &amp; Watch video game released in 1984. It's model number is UD-202. In the game, crabs are moving towards your character. You must push them away and not let them pinch you. If three crabs pinch you, then it'll result in a game over, and you'll have to start over. There are four columns, each a different color (from left to right: purple, green, orange, and blue). The crabs will start to come from the top, and you'll have to move your character from left to right to push them away, though more and more will always come. The game was one of two Super Color games, the other being Spitball Sparky.</desc>
		<releasedate>19840221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Casual Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_climbern.zip</path>
		<name>Climber</name>
		<desc>In Climber, you are a child known as Climber who, with the help of Lord Meiji's teachings, jumps across platforms trying to get to the top of Block Mountain while avoiding enemies and platforms that move. The enemies are the Blockmen, which walk and turn into block platforms when they reach a gap; Eyerom, birds that fly and get in the Climber's way; and thorny plants, which are obstacles in the way of Climber's movements. In each set of 5 levels, the first 4 ends with a bonus game where Climber has 2 chances to time his jump to catch Hentori, the bonus bird. On the fifth level, Climber must jump and grab the sword at the correct time to stab and defeat Dragalo the dragon.</desc>
		<releasedate>19880308T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_dkcirc.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Circus</name>
		<desc>Donkey Kong juggles pineapples while balancing on a barrel. Catch the pineapples, but beware of fireballs. Donkey Kong will automatically toss the pineapples he catches. Mario watches his juggling performance. Lives are lost either if a pineapple falls on the floor or if Donkey Kong touches a fireball. Mario laughs at Donkey Kong as he misses. Three misses and game ends. 1 point for each pineapple Donkey Kong catches and tosses. Maximum displayed score is 999. At 300 points fanfare sounds and all misses are canceled. If there are no misses when 300 points are reached, game goes into "Chance-Time": all points are awarded at double value (2 points per pineapple caught) until a miss is made.</desc>
		<releasedate>19840906T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_dkhockey.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Hockey</name>
		<desc> Donkey Kong Hockey features an ice rink for a hockey game between Mario and Donkey Kong. Each character has to try to throw as many hockey pucks as possible in his opponent's goal, whilst staying on his own side. Though limited, the movement of the player allows you to change the speed of the pucks. The first to score ten times is declared winner. In some cases the referee blocks the pucks or mysterious "Crazy Spots" appear on the rink, modifying the trajectories. Game A has you play against the CPU, whilst Game B gives two players the opportunity to take part in a battle against each other.</desc>
		<releasedate>19841113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Hockey</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_dkong3.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong 3</name>
		<desc>Just like in the arcade version, Donkey Kong breaks into Stanley's greenhouse, but both are now armed with sprayers. Using their sprayers, they attempt to force bees to sting each other.</desc>
		<releasedate>19840801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_egg.zip</path>
		<name>Egg</name>
		<desc>Chickens lay eggs. Control the wolf so that he catches them in his cap. When the wolf drops an egg, one miss is scored. The cock appears/disappears at every five seconds. When the cock appears while egg falls, half miss is scored (miss mark blinks). Three full misses and game is over. 1 point per caught egg. At 200 and 500 points, if there are one or more misses, fanfare sounds and all misses are canceled.</desc>
		<releasedate>19811009T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Casual Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_fireatk.zip</path>
		<name>Fire Attack</name>
		<desc>The Game &amp; Watch game Fire Attack, released March 26, 1982, was a game where your character is a civil war-looking general, trying to defend his fort from an onslaught of Native Americans attacking with flaming torches.</desc>
		<releasedate>19820326T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_fires.zip</path>
		<name>Fire</name>
		<desc>People jump from a burning building. Underneath, two rescuers are holding a net. The aim of the game is to catch these people and bounce them into an ambulance. Each time a person bounces off the net, they bounce to the right. It takes three bounces to save a person. If you accidentally drop a person, you lose a life. After 3 lives are lost, the game is over.
The game's sound effects are an important part of the gameplay and let you know when someone has just jumped, when there are several people bouncing in the air, when someone has been dropped or, most importantly, when someone has hit the net.</desc>
		<releasedate>19800731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_flagman.zip</path>
		<name>Flagman</name>
		<desc>Game of memory and reflexes, two game modes exist:

In Game A mode, you must raise the flags in the order indicated by Flagman, and this within the time limit.
In Game B mode, you must raise the flags corresponding to the numbers indicated, only one at a time.
Rules common to both modes:

The player starts with three lives.
The more the player advances in the game, the more difficult it becomes.
If he presses the wrong button, he loses a life.
The game ends once the three lives are lost.</desc>
		<releasedate>19800605T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_gcliff.zip</path>
		<name>Gold Cliff</name>
		<desc>You play as an archaeologist on his way to many expeditions. In order to reach the treasures, you'll need to avoid the enemies as well as precisely jump on the many disappearing platforms, whilst not forgetting the key to unlock the door on the upper levels. After a few levels the explorer faces the guardian of the temple which must be defeated to progress further. Gold Cliff is composed of 24 worlds and 144 different levels and is the first G&amp;W game to feature a "continue" option.</desc>
		<releasedate>19881019T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_helmeto.zip</path>
		<name>Helmet</name>
		<desc>In the game, you have to run from one house to the house across from it without getting hit by falling tools that your enemies is throwing at you. Sometimes the door on the other house will close, making you run around until it opens.</desc>
		<releasedate>19810221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_judgeo.zip</path>
		<name>Judge</name>
		<desc>The game can be played in two player mode or single player mode and starts with two characters facing each other in a duel of focus and reflexes. The player needs to wait for the two to each lift a sign reading a random number from 1 to 9. In single-player, if your player character shows a higher number than the CPU's, then you must push the hit button. If yours is the lower number however, then you must push the dodge/flee button. If you manage to hit your opponent before he could doge or avoid his attack, you will score points. Game B is used for playing against a fellow person instead of a CPU.</desc>
		<releasedate>19801004T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_lboat.zip</path>
		<name>Lifeboat</name>
		<desc>A fire breaks out on a luxury liner; passengers jump from the ship. Put lifeboat in position for catching passengers. Each lifeboat holds up to four passengers. There is a shore on the left and right of the screen. When a lifeboat reaches shore, passengers will unload automatically. 1 point per person caught. 1 point per person unloaded to shore. Maximum displayed score is 999. At 300 points fanfare sounds and all misses are canceled; if there are no misses when 300 points are reached game goes into "Chance-Time": score flashes and all points are awarded at double value (2 points per passenger caught or unloaded to shore) until a miss is made.</desc>
		<releasedate>19831016T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_lion.zip</path>
		<name>Lion</name>
		<desc>The aim of the game is to prevent the lions from escaping from their cage. The two zookeepers are controlled separately using the corresponding buttons. The lions will try to escape. To prevent this, place a guard in front of the lion. The lions may also try to "trick" the player. Each time you prevent a lion from escaping, you score one point. The maximum score is 999. If a lion escapes, an animation showing the zookeeper hiding in a tree is played and you get a fail. The game ends when you get three failures.</desc>
		<releasedate>19810101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_mariotj.zip</path>
		<name>Mario The Juggler</name>
		<desc>Mario the Juggler is a Game &amp; Watch system released as a part of the New Wide Screen series on October 14, 1991. It is a reworked version of 1980's Ball, with Mario themes replacing the original's generic juggler and his balls. It was the final Game &amp; Watch ever released.</desc>
		<releasedate>19911016T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_mickdon.zip</path>
		<name>Mickey and Donald</name>
		<desc>Mickey &amp; Donald is the third game in the fourth (and biggest) series of Game &amp; Watch games published by Nintendo, also known as the Multi Screen Series, consisting of 15 titles.
You'l control both Mickey and Donald acting as firefighters, subduing a six story building fire. Mickey can go up and down to fix various leak in the hose, whilst Donald can be moved left and right to subdue the flames. All has to be done, while making sure Goofy doesn't fall asleep. When the flames are finally out, Minnie pops in to give Mickey some hugs and kisses. On the other hand, if the flames reach the top of the building then Donald's tail will burst into flame!</desc>
		<releasedate>19821112T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_opanic.zip</path>
		<name>Oil Panic</name>
		<desc>You play as character on the upper screen needing to collect and catch droplets of oil coming from a pipe on the ceiling with your bucket. When filled with three drops of oil, you'll need to rush towards the balcony to pass over the liquid to the randomly moving second character on the lower floor. One has to be careful on keeping an eye towards the second character, since missing his actions might result in covering innocent gas station customers in oil. Game A and B are practically identical, although game B ups the ante by faster movements and irregular action of the second characters and infrequent customers.</desc>
		<releasedate>19820528T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_pchute.zip</path>
		<name>Parachute</name>
		<desc>Skydivers come parachuting down over shark-infested waters. Lifeboat tries to catch them. Try to catch skydivers. Move boat left or right by pressing corresponding control buttons. When a skydiver falls into the ocean he is attacked by sharks. Three misses and game ends. 1 point is scored for each skydiver caught by lifeboat. Maximum displayed score is 999. When the score reaches a bonus score (200 or 500 points), any miss marks indicated at the time are erased with a fanfare and game continues.</desc>
		<releasedate>19810619T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_pinball.zip</path>
		<name>Pinball</name>
		<desc>It's basically just a portable pinball game where you control two flippers. The goal is to keep the ball above the flippers by hitting it. The ball will then go in a fairly random direction and hit the bumpers, thus giving the player points.</desc>
		<releasedate>19831205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Pinball</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_popeye.zip</path>
		<name>Popeye</name>
		<desc>One plays as Popeye the sailor, needing to catch objects thrown from the wharf by Olive Oil. If the player misses one, it falls into the sea, which results in half a miss. At certain points Bluto will be trying to punch Popeye as he appears from the left side of the screen. If Bluto hits Popeye he will fall into the water and lose a life. In Game B Bluto can appear from both sides of the screen.</desc>
		<releasedate>19810805T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_popeyep.zip</path>
		<name>Popeye</name>
		<desc>One plays as Popeye the sailor, needing to catch objects thrown from the wharf by Olive Oil. If the player misses one, it falls into the sea, which results in half a miss. At certain points Bluto will be trying to punch Popeye as he appears from the left side of the screen. If Bluto hits Popeye he will fall into the water and lose a life. In Game B Bluto can appear from both sides of the screen.</desc>
		<releasedate>19810805T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_rshower.zip</path>
		<name>Rain Shower</name>
		<desc>You play as a character trying to dry his laundry out in his yard. One has to constantly go back and forth between the two floors of your house and pull one of the four strings from left to right to prevent the water to fall on your clothes. Every 100 points the sun will come back and give you a few seconds of peace. Game B will add crows which will sometimes pull the strings the opposite way.</desc>
		<releasedate>19831008T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_smbn.zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario Bros.</name>
		<desc>Mario must rescue Princess Toadstool, who has been captured by Bowser, King Koopa. To do this, he has to go through 8 distinct levels. Some of them scroll from right to left, others are static screens, but are then timed.</desc>
		<releasedate>19880308T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_snoopyp.zip</path>
		<name>Snoopy (panorama Screen)</name>
		<desc>Shroeder is playing his piano. The notes fly through the air to where Woodstock is sleeping. Operate Snoopy left and right to strike down the notes with his hammer so that Woodstock may sleep in peace. If a note gets to any nest, a miss occurs; three misses and game ends. Game A: 3 lines of notes. Game B: 4 lines of notes. 1 point for each note knocked down. At 300 points a music is played and all misses are canceled; if there are no misses when 300 points are reached game goes into "Chance-Time": score flashes and all points are awarded at double value until miss is made. Maximum display score is 999 points. At 999 points score resets and game starts again (at higher speed).</desc>
		<releasedate>19830830T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_squish.zip</path>
		<name>Squish</name>
		<desc>Squish is a Game &amp; Watch game similar to Devil World. The upper screen features the character Grumpy manipulating a total of four buttons. These move the walls in the desired direction. You play as Ziggy, trapped in the bottom screen, with the goal to control him and to make sure he doesn't get squashed between two walls. Game B slightly differs from the concept in Game A, as an addition you'll have to try to capture four "Maze Bugs", each located in a corner of a room.</desc>
		<releasedate>19860417T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20231230T104051</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_ssparky.zip</path>
		<name>Spitball Sparky</name>
		<desc>Spitball Sparky 's gameplay is similar to the game Breakout, where the player controls Sparky, a small character with a trumpet shaped mouth, catching and spitting a ball capable of destroying the on-screen blocks. As one progresses further into the game, the walls start moving or increase their numbers. One can control the ball even before it reaches Sparky's mouth and apply a different force by adjusting the character's breath. In Game B, certain blocks blink and require two hits before they disappear.</desc>
		<releasedate>19840207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Breakout games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_stennis.zip</path>
		<name>Snoopy Tennis</name>
		<desc>Charlie Brown and Snoopy are playing tennis. Snoopy has to climb the tree to receive Charlie Brown's serve. Lucy keeps butting in, intercepts the ball from snoopy and returns it. Pressing when ball is just in front of Snoopy's face is good timing.  When Snoopy swings and misses, he can not move until his racket returns to original position. When Snoopy misses, ball continues on, followed by sound of broken bottles. CRASH mark appears. Snoopy pretends innocence, fakes sleep. Charlie Brown throws racket down in despair. 2 points when returning Charlie Brown's ball. 3 points when returning Lucy's ball. Bonus scores are those with 200 or 500 points (200, 500, 1200, 1500, ... to 9500). When each bonus score is reached, fanfare sounds and all misses are canceled. When a bonus score is reached and there are no misses registered, game goes into "Chance time" for 50 to 70 seconds. Score flashes on and off, returning Charlie Brown's ball score 5 points, Lucy's ball score 6 points. Maximum display score is 9999 points.</desc>
		<releasedate>19820428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20231230T104010</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_tbridge.zip</path>
		<name>Turtle Bridge</name>
		<desc>Tourists attempt to cross a lake from left bank to right bank with their luggage by stepping on the backs of turtles. When tourist reaches other side he hands his baggage to other tourist then crosses back again. When turtle sees a fish rising to the surface, it dives down into the water. When the tourist is on a turtle that dives, score one miss; miss mark appears on screen; three misses and game ends. Once tourist leaves the left bank, he can not climb back without his baggage to other tourist. Fishes do not rise from the center of screen in Game A. If tourist remains in center area for more than 2 minutes, fish begins rising from center also. 3 points each time tourist hand over a piece of baggage. Extra points are scored each time tourist returns to left bank. The faster the tourist makes the round trip, the higher the score (Max. points: 12. Min. points: 2). When player reaches a bonus score (successive units of 200 or 500), any miss marks indicated at the time are erased with a fanfare and game continues. If a bonus score is reached with no misses, game goes into Chance time for 20 to 40 seconds. Turtles do not move and fishes do not appear. Maximum display score is 9999 points.</desc>
		<releasedate>19820201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_tfish.zip</path>
		<name>Tropical Fish</name>
		<desc>In the game, the player will transfer fish from one aquarium to another one via a fishbowl in a game similar to the previously released Fire. If a fish drops on the floor, the cat (similar in appearance to the one from Chef) will take it for himself as a tasty snack. The cat also appears as the alarm clock icon. When the game begins, fish will start jumping from the water tank on the right. As the player, they must make sure that they catch the fish in the fishbowl. Shortly after this, the fish will jump from the water bowl to the left, and the player will have to keep on catching it until it reaches the other water tank.</desc>
		<releasedate>19850701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_vermin.zip</path>
		<name>Vermin</name>
		<desc>Players attain points by clobbering moles that emerge from the ground. The moles are attempting to destroy the main character's garden, and it is the player's goal to make sure they don't do this. The player can accomplish this by moving the character (described in the manual as a puppet) via the left and right buttons on the hardware. If the hammer is above the hole where a mole is about to surface, it will automatically smash the creature, thus rewarding the player with a point. As the player progresses, the speed of the game increases. If a mole makes it through the hole unscathed, it will result in a lost life for the player. After three moles get through, the game is over and the player must restart it.</desc>
		<releasedate>19800710T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Casual Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_zelda.zip</path>
		<name>Zelda</name>
		<desc>In the game, the player controls Link. In the game's world, eight dragons have been causing havoc and have refused to make peace with the men. After kidnapping Princess Zelda, Link decides to go off and slay the dragons and save the princess.

The game mostly consists of combat. In each dungeon, Link battles several Goblins. After defeating a Goblin, it may drop an item, and stairs will appear that will allow Link to progress to the next room. Once Link gets to the Dragon's lair, he will have to defeat the Dragon in order to obtain a fragment of the Triforce. The player will have to repeat this process eight times. After the eighth fragment is obtained, Link can use the completed Triforce to save Princess Zelda.</desc>
		<releasedate>19890826T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20231230T104113</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_manhole.zip</path>
		<name>Manhole</name>
		<desc>The gameplay features a character, using simple plates, to help people crossing the road unharmed at two different heights/levels. With time the frequency of people and their speed will increase. Game B, doesn't set itself apart from Game A, apart from more people crossing the roads at the beginning and a quicker onset of pace and frequency of people. The game Manhole is the first G&amp;W to ever feature an extra live bonus system. Every 200 or 500 points (depending on the game-type), a little tune will indicate that one or more "misses" will be forgiven.</desc>
		<releasedate>19810127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20231230T114922</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_manholeg.zip</path>
		<name>Manhole</name>
		<desc>The gameplay features a character, using simple plates, to help people crossing the road unharmed at two different heights/levels. With time the frequency of people and their speed will increase. Game B, doesn't set itself apart from Game A, apart from more people crossing the roads at the beginning and a quicker onset of pace and frequency of people. The game Manhole is the first G&amp;W to ever feature an extra live bonus system. Every 200 or 500 points (depending on the game-type), a little tune will indicate that one or more "misses" will be forgiven.</desc>
		<releasedate>19810127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20231230T115134</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_sbuster.zip</path>
		<name>Safe Buster</name>
		<desc>You play as a guard trying to stop Willy Bomber, a bandit throwing explosives from the roof of a bank, trying to bust its safe. With a very large tube, you'll have to intercept the bombs and dump them on the side of the screen with a maximum of three bombs at the time. This G&amp;W game show much similarities in collecting/dumping access materials just like Oil Panic. The more explosives you unload on the left, then the greater your chance to make the torch (on the left part of the screen) bounce to the upper screen, therefore reaching Willy's crate of bombs, resulting in a massive explosion. Game B adds the difficulty the appearance of a cover at irregular intervals on the left side of the screen, preventing you from unloading the bombs for a few seconds</desc>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20231230T212920</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_dkong.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong</name>
		<desc>Move Mario to make him rescue his girlfriend, kidnapped by Donkey Kong. In odd levels, Donkey Kong throws barrels at Mario. Operate Mario and take him to the top of the building, making him avoid barrels. In even levels, operate Mario in order to remove all rivets from the girders by walking above them. Fireballs hang around: be sure Mario won't touch them! Additional info: don't let Mario move too left or right of the girders or he'll fall down; the left ladder on the second girder is a "safe position" from barrels; Mario can walk, not jump through the electric fence below Donkey Kong.</desc>
		<releasedate>20020409T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coleco Industries, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco Industries, Inc.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20240105T185831</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_dkjr.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Jr (New Wide Screen)</name>
		<desc>Game &amp; Watch Wide Screen: Donkey Kong Jr. is the first game in the fifth series of Game &amp; Watch games published by Nintendo, also known as the (New) Wide Screen Series, consisting of 8 titles. More colorful and child-friendly, the models from the New Wide Screen series (still described as Wide Screen on the boxes) aren't much different from the previous line of G&amp;W games, save for a cheaper price and a different shell design.
Donkey Kong Jr. is a semi-direct port from the Famicom game Donkey Kong Jr. and can be classified as the direct sequel to Donkey Kong 2 from the Multi Screen series. Mario who once again has come back to capture Donkey Kong and put him in a cage. The player controls Junior who has to set his father free. In order to succeed, one must control Junior by jumping and climbing vines and disarm traps by falling coconuts, whilst avoiding crows. The ultimate goal is to secure a key to open the lock on the cage. Game A and B only differ by the time Junior can stay hanging on a vine. 
By pressing Game A and Game B simultaneously the best score will appear on the screen. This function will be featured in almost every G&amp;W game from then on. This model is also the G&amp;W game with the most buttons (10), including Alarm and ACL.</desc>
		<releasedate>19821026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20240111T120842</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_dkjrp.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Jr. (panorama Screen)</name>
		<desc>Donkey Kong has been captured and chained by Mario. Donkey Kong Jr. goes to papa's rescue with key he needs to open the locks on the chains. Junior is attacked by fierce birds. He uses umbrellas to leap from heights, and balloons to get up there, opening the locks on the way. When he opens all 4 locks, papa is free. Each time he opens one lock, he must go back to START to retrieve the key, then sets out again is lost. With three misses game ends. 1 point when Junior jumps to umbrella or balloon. 2 to 10 points when Junior hits fierce bird with coconut. 10 points when Junior opens one lock. 10 points (extra bonus) when Junior opens all four locks. When score reaches 300 points and there are one or two misses, all the misses are cleared with fanfare. If there are no misses when a 300 score is reached, game goes into "CHANCE TIME". Score flashes and all the points are awarded at double value until a miss is scored. Maximum displayed score is 999 points. At 999 points score resets and game starts again (at higher speed).</desc>
		<releasedate>19821026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20240111T121540</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_ghouse.zip</path>
		<name>Green House</name>
		<desc>You play as the gardener Stanley the Bugman defending his greenhouse from various parasites. You have to kill the numerous spiders and caterpillars/worms approaching your flowers, by pressing the "spray" button to use your insecticide. The spiders attack from above whilst the caterpillars/worm attack from below. When three flowers are eating the game will end.</desc>
		<releasedate>19821206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20240111T122528</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_mario.zip</path>
		<name>Mario Bros.</name>
		<desc>Mario is back in action with his brother Luigi, working in a bottling plant, loading cases on a belt conveyor. The conveyor carries the cases up for loading onto trucks. Operate Mario and Luigi up and down ladders in order to get cases. When a case is dropped, the foreman get angry and a miss is scored. Three misses and game is over 1 point per case loaded on a conveyor. 10 points per truck loaded with 8 cases. At 300 points fanfare sounds and all misses are canceled; if there are no misses when 300 points are reached, game goes into "CHANCE TIME". Score flashes and all points are awarded at double value until a miss is made. Maximum displayed score is 999 points.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19830314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20240111T123341</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_dkong2.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong II</name>
		<desc>A continuation of the famous Donkey Kong Story. Now Mario has chained Donkey Kong. Donkey Kong Junior braves snapjaws, sparks and birds, throwing the key which will open Donkey Kong's locks, up to where his papa is held prisoner. Avoid sparks overhead and make Junior jump and throw key to upper screen. When a snapjaw attacks, make Junior jump without hitting overhead spark. When Junior reaches the upper screen, he has to jump to get the key he threw again. The key jumps to one of the four locks.
- Press top of "PLUS" button when on top of chain. A lock opens.</desc>
		<releasedate>19830307T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20240111T125020</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_mariocm.zip</path>
		<name>Mario's Cement Factory (New Wide Screen)</name>
		<desc>The player controls Mario working in a cement factory, where one has to make sure the cement carried from the top of the screen reaches one of the two concrete mixers on the lower corners of the screen safely. The cement can't go directly into the mixers though. It must first go through four tanks which Mario can open by activating levers. His task is to go back and forth between all four spots and release the concrete before anything is spilled. Failure to do so will result in dumping of said concrete on the truckers waiting to make their delivery. To reach the different levers Mario must travel between floors via elevators, which must be taken carefully to avoid Mario falling off. Apart from a higher difficulty in Game B, nothing chances between the two game models.</desc>
		<releasedate>19830616T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20240111T130250</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_mariocmt.zip</path>
		<name>Mario's Cement Factory (Table Top)</name>
		<desc>In the game, you control a character in a cement factory. You start at the upper left hand corner of the screen. In the middle, platforms are dropping down on the left side and going up on the right side. Meanwhile, buckets of cement are about to go in the mixers, though there are machines blocking the cement so that they can't go all of the way down. As the player, you have to make sure that the machines don't overflow with cement, and use the lever to make the cement drop the machine below. After you pull the other lever, then the cement will go into the mixer. There are four machines, two on each side. If you fall into the middle without a platform there to support you, then you will loose a life. If the machine fills up with too much cement, then you will also loose a life.</desc>
		<releasedate>19830428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>4</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20240111T130405</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gnw_mbaway.zip</path>
		<name>Mario's Bombs Away</name>
		<desc>Mario is in the jungle, fighting against an enemy army. His aim is to take five bombs on the right side of the jungle. Mario's companion on the right side places bombs close to enemies. When all five bombs are in place, they detonate and enemy army is beaten. Enemies try to light Mario's bomb; lift/lower Mario's bomb to keep it safe. If enemies torches reach Mario's bomb, all progress (bombs already placed) is lost. Three misses and game ends. 1 point when Mario steps forward. 5 points when Mario places a bomb. 10 points when Mario places the 5th bomb. At 300 points a music is played and all misses are canceled; if there are no misses when 300 points are reached game goes into "Chance-Time": score flashes and all points are awarded at double value until miss is made. Maximum displayed score is 999 points. At 999 points score resets and game starts again (at higher speed).</desc>
		<releasedate>19831110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20240111T131803</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
